nt.vc 2016-11-28

# House of Next Tuesday

## Privacy Policy

All references to Next Tuesday, “we” or “us” in this Privacy Policy shall refer only to Next Tuesday GmbH. AdMetrics is a service provided by us, which enables our clients to report on ad delivery and performance by making use of web beacons and log files. 

### Definitions

#### Ad Delivery and Reporting

Ad Delivery and Reporting is separate and distinct from Internet-Based Advertising and means the logging of page views or the collection of other information about a computer or device for the purpose of delivering ads or providing advertising-related services, including but not limited to: providing a specific advertisement based on a particular type of browser or time of day; statistical reporting in connection with the activity on a website; analytics and analysis; optimization of location of ad placement; ad performance; reach and frequency metrics (e.g., frequency capping); security and fraud prevention; billing; and logging the number and type of ads served on a particular day to a particular website. 

#### Personally identifiable Information (PII)

Personally identifiable information (PII) is any information used or intended to be used to identify a particular individual, including name, address, telephone number, email address, financial account number, and government-issued identifier. 

#### Non-PII

Non-Pii is data that is not PII as defined in the NAI Code, but that is linked or reasonably linkable to a particular computer or device. Non-PII includes, but is not limited to, unique identifiers associated with user's computers or devices and IP addresses, where such identifiers associated with users' computers or devices and IP addresses, where such identifiers or IP addresses are not linked to PII. Non-PII does not include De-Identified Data. 

#### Cookie

A cookie is a small text file that is stored in a web browser by a website or ad server. By saving information in a cookie, websites and servers can remember preferences or recognize browsers from one visit to another or from one website to another. A 

#### De-identified data

De-identified data is data that is not linked or reasonable linkable to an individual or to a particular computer or device. 

#### Beacons

Web beacons are electronic files used to track your navigation of a website or collection of sites, the completion of transactions, submittal of applications and browsing behavior. 

#### Log files

Log files track actions occurring on Sites and collect data including, as an example, your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, click data and types of advertisements viewed. 

### Privacy Statement

This privacy statement describes our practices and policies with regard to the information that is collected by this service. It applies only to Next Tuesday. It does not state the use practices or policies of our clients, of the websites on which ads are shown, or of other parties. 

#### Information NOT Collected - PII

We do not collect personally identifiable information (data collected with an intention to identify and contact a person such as name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or ip adresses). 

#### Information Collected - Non-PII

The non-personally identifiable information we collect includes browser type, operating system, domain name and access and visibility dates and durations. We use web beacons to collect this data from your web browser. We do not make use of cookies to collect this data. 

#### How Used

We use your Non-PII (Information) to measure and report on the the performance of advertising displayed to you on third party web-sites. 

#### Sharing this Information

We may share this performance data collected with our business partners and clients. 

#### Security

We use reasonable and appropriate security measures to protect the data collected. 

#### Changes

We may change the Privacy Policy at any time by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Website and if such changes are material, a notice of the changes will also be posted along with the revised Privacy Policy. 

sss 

### Questions?

Email

Office address

Next Tuesday GmbH  
Hanauer Landstrasse 161-173  
60314 Frankfurt/Main  
Germany 

Next Tuesday GmbH  
Managing directors, responsible according to § 6 Abs.2 MDStV: Martin Einsporn, Thomas Einsporn, Markus Repetschnig  
Registry court: Frankfurt am Main  
Commercial register: HRB 53289  
VAT Id. DE 217325167
